A Guide to the Richmond YWCA records, 1901-2002
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series 3: Facility, Infrastructure, and Renovation Records, 1978-2001
  - Renovation - Invoices including Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 7:29)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Certificate for Payment, 2000 (Box-folder 7:30)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Contract, 2000 (Box-folder 7:31)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Construction Proposal, 2000 (Box-folder 7:32)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Correspondence and Quotes, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7:33)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Design Development Budget, 2000 (Box-folder 7:34)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Financial Statements, 1999 (Box-folder 7:35)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Owner/Architect/Contractor Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 7:36)
  - Renovation - Kjellstrom and Lee Construction - Request for Information, undated (Box-folder 7:37)
  - Renovation - Monument Group, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7:38)
  - Renovation - Permits - Applications and Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 7:39)
  - Renovation - Relocation - Lease Agreements, and Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 7:40)
  - Renovation - Richmond Shelter - Capital Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 7:41)
  - Renovation - Scribner, Messer, Brady and Wade P.C. Architects - Space Needs Analysis, 1993 (Box-folder 7:42)
  - Renovation - Space Planning Magazine Articles, undated (Box-folder 7:43)
  - Renovation - YWCA Assignment of Contract, 2001 (Box-folder 7:44)
  - Renovation - YWCA Capital Campaign Projections, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7:45)
  - Renovation - YWCA Renovation Feasibility Study, 1998 (Box-folder 7:46)
- Series 4: Financial Records and Materials, 1917-1975
  - Treasurer's Report, 1916 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Budget, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Budget, 1919 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1919 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Budget, 1920 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1920 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Budget, 1921 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Financial Report - Walford, 1921 (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1921 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Annual Report, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Budget, 1922 (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Financial Reports including Annual Reports, Statement and Treasurer's Report, 1922 (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Financial Report - Walford, 1922 (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Budget, 1923 (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Financial Report - Walford, 1923 (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1923 (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Budget, 1924 (Box-folder 8:17)
  - Budget, 1925 (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Budget, 1926 (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Budget, 1927 (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Budget, 1928 (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Budget, 1929 (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Budget including Revised Budget and Summary, 1930 (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Budget including Summary and Revisions, 1931 (Box-folder 8:24)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1931 (Box-folder 8:25)
  - Budget including Summary and Revised Budget, 1932 (Box-folder 8:26)
  - Financial Statement and Treasurer's Reports, 1932 (Box-folder 8:27)
  - Budget including Summary, Revised Summary and Estimated Budget, 1933 (Box-folder 8:28)
  - Financial Condition, Operating Statement and Treasurer's Report, 1933 (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Financial Reports including Summary Reports, 1933 (Box-folder 8:30)
  - Annual Report, Financial Condition and Operating Statement, 1934 (Box-folder 8:31)
  - Budget including Original, Summary and Revised Budget, 1934 (Box-folder 8:32)
  - Financial Committee Report, Financial Condition and Operating Statement, 1935 (Box-folder 8:33)
  - Financial Condition and Budget including Summary and Revised Budget, 1935 (Box-folder 8:34)
  - Budget, 1936 (Box-folder 8:35)
  - Financial Condition and Operating Statement, 1936 (Box-folder 8:36)
  - Budget, 1937 (Box-folder 8:37)
  - Financial Condition and Operating Statement, 1937 (Box-folder 8:38)
  - Annual Report, Operating Statement, Financial Condition and Treasurer's Reports, 1938 (Box-folder 8:39)
  - Budget, 1938 (Box-folder 8:40)
  - Budget, 1939 (Box-folder 8:41)
  - Treasurer's Reports and Operating Statements, 1939 (Box-folder 8:42)
  - Budget, 1940 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Finance Committee Report for Annual Meeting, Operating Statement and Treasurer's Reports, 1940 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Budget, 1941 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Operating Statement and Treasurer's Reports, 1941 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Budget, 1942 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Operating Statements and Treasurer's Reports, 1942 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Budget, 1943 (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Operating Statements and Treasurer's Reports, 1943 (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Budget, 1944 (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Treasurer's Reports including Financial Reports, 1944 (Box-folder 9:10-9:11)
  - Budget, 1945 (Box-folder 9:12-9:13)
  - Financial Reports and Treasurer's Reports, 1945 (Box-folder 9:14)
  - Budget, 1946 (Box-folder 9:15)
  - Treasurer's Reports and Financial Reports, 1946 (Box-folder 9:16)
  - Budget including Reports and Correspondence, 1947 (Box-folder 9:17)
  - Budget including Work Sheet Budgets and Reports, 1948 (Box-folder 9:18)
  - Budget including Correspondence, Notes and Reports, 1949 (Box-folder 9:19)
  - Treasurer's Report including Departmental Financial Reports, 1956 (Box-folder 9:20)
  - Budget, 1970 (Box-folder 9:21)
  - Budget, 1971 (Box-folder 9:22)
  - Budget and Finance Report, 1972 (Box-folder 9:23)
  - Budget and Finance Report, 1973 (Box-folder 9:24)
  - Budget and Finance Report, 1974 (Box-folder 9:25)
  - Budget, 1975 (Box-folder 9:26)
- Series 5: Other Financial Records, 1905-2001
  - Auditor's Reports, 1912-1920 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Bonds and Notes, 1925, 1934 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Cash Payroll Vouchers - Central and Walford, 1953 (Box-folder 10:3-10:5)
  - Cash Payroll Vouchers - Central and Walford, 1954 (Box-folder 10:6-10:7)
  - Cash Payroll Vouchers - Central and Walford, 1955 (Box-folder 10:8-10:9)
  - Checks and Notes issued to Banks, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Checks and Notes issued to State Planters Bank and Trust Company, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Contributions from Churches, Agency, Clubs and Groups, and Individuals, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 10:12)
  - Contributions, 1983 (Box-folder 10:13)
  - Contributions, 1984, undated (Box-folder 10:14)
  - Contributions, 1985 (Box-folder 10:15)
  - Finance - Computer System/Finance Software, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Fundraising - Rebuilding Hope Capital Campaign, undated (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Lumsden Fund - Checks and Bank Records, 1947 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Lumsden Fund - Checks and Bank Records, 1948 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Lumsden Fund - Checks and Bank Records, 1949 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Lumsden Fund - Checks and Bank Records, 1950 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Lumsden Fund - Financial Reports, 1946 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Lumsden Fund - Financial Reports and Records, 1947 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Proposals for Audit and Tax Services, 1993 (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Receipts and Records of Payment, 1911-1915, 1947, undated (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Reports and Records on work with Individuals, 1933 (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Reports including Central Building report and reports on work with individuals, 1934 (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Richmond YWCA Building Fund, 1911, 1913 (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Round the World YWCA, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 11:14)
  - Withholding Tax Record, 1944 (Box-folder 11:15)
  - YWCA Building Fund - Checks and Notes, 1905-1913 (Box-folder 11:16)
  - YWCA Finance Manual, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 11:17-11:18)
  - YWCA Issued Checks and Bank Records, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 11:19)
- Series 6: Other Financial Records - Richmond Community Fund, 1925-1949
  - Richmond Community Fund - Income and Expense Budget, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Income and Expense Budget, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Income and Expense Budget, 1940 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Newspaper Clippings, 1929 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1925 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1926 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1927 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1928 (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1929 (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1930 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1931 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1932 (Box-folder 12:12)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1933 (Box-folder 12:13)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1934 (Box-folder 12:14)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1935 (Box-folder 12:15)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1936 (Box-folder 12:16)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1937 (Box-folder 12:17)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1938 (Box-folder 12:18)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1939 (Box-folder 12:19)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1940 (Box-folder 12:20)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1941 (Box-folder 12:21)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1942 (Box-folder 12:22)
  - Richmond Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1943 (Box-folder 12:23)
  - Richmond War and Community Fund - Reports of Current Income and Expense, 1944 (Box-folder 12:24)
  - Richmond War and Community Fund - Monthly Requisition Forms, 1945 (Box-folder 12:25)
  - Richmond War and Community Fund - Monthly Requisition Forms, 1946 (Box-folder 12:26)
  - Richmond War and Community Fund - Annual Budget Report Forms, 1947 (Box-folder 12:27)
  - Richmond Area Community Chest - Monthly Requisition Forms, 1947 (Box-folder 12:28)
  - Richmond War and Community Fund - Annual Budget Report, 1948 (Box-folder 12:29)
  - Richmond Area Community Chest - Monthly Requisition Forms, 1948 (Box-folder 12:30)
  - Richmond Area Community Chest - Annual Budget Report, 1949 (Box-folder 12:31)
  - Richmond Community Fund Solicitor's Manual, 1928 (Box-folder 12:32)
  - Richmond Community Fund Worker's Manual, 1933, 1937 (Box-folder 12:33)
- Series 7: Papers on YWCA Properties, 1907-1986
  - Abstract of Title - John B. Swartwout on 213 and 215 East Franklin Street, undated (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Camp Fernlake - Deeds, Agreement Contract, Lien Waver and Lawyers Title Insurance, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Camp Fernlake - Reports, Records, Notes and Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Camp Fernlake - Sale - Correspondence, Contract and Settlement Statements, 1986 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Contract of Sale of YWCA's Building and Lots on 709 and 711 East Franklin Street with Preston and Inez Cobb, 1911 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Construction - Contract with the Architectural firm, Noland and Baskervill, undated (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Construction - Fifth Street Building - Fixtures - Payments made to Catlett Electric, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Construction - Fifth Street Building - Payments made to H.L. Matthews, Contractor and Builder, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Construction - Noland and Baskervill, Architects - Correspondence on the Construction of YWCA Building (North Fifth Street), 1913-1914 (Box-folder 13:9)
  - Construction - Uniform Contract Agreement - YWCA and H.L. Matthews, 1913 (Box-folder 13:10)
  - Construction - YWCA Boarding Home - Payments made to E.C. Wood, Contractor and Builder, 1912-1913 (Box-folder 13:11)
  - Correspondence Regarding YWCA Properties, 1901-1921, undated (Box-folder 13:12)
  - Deed of Bargain and Sale, 1919, 1962 (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Deed of Lease between YWCA and Nancy R. and Thomas L. Jeter and Son, 1949 (Box-folder 13:14)
  - Deed of Lease and Papers, 1913-1962 (Box-folder 13:15)
  - Deed of Trust - J.M. Fourqurean to R.A. Lancaster, 1907 (Box-folder 13:16)
  - Deed of Trust - Mattie C. Hawes to YWCA, 1918 (Box-folder 13:17)
  - Deed of Trust - YWCA to State Planters Bank and Trust Company, 1931 (Box-folder 13:18)
  - Deed of Trust - YWCA to John C. Williams, 1936 (Box-folder 13:19)
  - Hedge Lawn Property (Camp) - Final Paymnet made by Laburnum realty Corporation for Mr. Powell's Note, 1941 (Box-folder 13:20)
  - Inventories - YWCA Building Contents and Domestic Science Department, 1915-1916, undated (Box-folder 13:21)
  - Memorandum of Agreement YWCA with John B. Swartwout, 1911 (Box-folder 13:22)
  - Minutes - Special Meeting on the Sale of YWCA Property to Hugh M. Taylor, 1912 (Box-folder 13:23)
  - Minutes - Special Meeting on the Sale of YWCA Real Estate on 709 and 711 East Franklin Street, 1911 (Box-folder 13:24)
  - Mount Vernon Property (213-215 East Franklin Street, Richmond, VA.) - YWCA Statement of Settlement with John B. Swartwout, undated (Box-folder 13:25)
  - Otis Elevator Company - Specification and Proposal for one electric passenger elevator, 1914 (Box-folder 13:26)
  - Papers on YWCA Property - 5 West Cary Street, 1917-1925, undated (Box-folder 13:27)
  - Papers on YWCA Property/Building - 108 West Cary Street, 1912-1915, 1926 (Box-folder 13:28)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Building - Deeds and Papers, 1913-1922 (Box-folder 13:29)
  - Utilities for YWCA Properies, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 13:30)
  - Walford Building - Deed, Abstract of Title and Papers, 1925-1946, undated (Box-folder 13:31)
  - YWCA Property - Lot on Fifth Street - Memorandum, and Preamble and Resolution, 1914, 1916 (Box-folder 13:32)
- Series 8: Staff, 1971-1992
  - General Staff - Materials and Notes, 1978 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - General Staff - Staff List, Correspondence, Minutes and Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - General Staff - Staff List, Correspondence, Minutes and Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - General Staff - Staff List, Correspondence, Minutes and Materials, 1981 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - General Staff - Staff List, Correspondence, Minutes and Materials, 1982 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - General Staff - YWCA Staff List, Correspondence, Minutes and Records, 1983 (Box-folder 14:6)
  - General Staff - YWCA Staff List, Correspondence and Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 14:7)
  - General Staff - YWCA Staff List, Calendar and Correspondence with Attachments, 1985 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - General Staff - Correspondence with attachments, 1986 (Box-folder 14:9)
  - General Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 14:10)
  - General Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1988 (Box-folder 14:11)
  - General Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 14:12)
  - General Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1990 (Box-folder 14:13)
  - General Staff - Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 14:14)
  - General Staff - Correspondence and Executive Director's Reports, January-March, 1992 (Box-folder 14:15)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 14:16)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 14:17)
  - Program Staff - Minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 14:18)
  - Program Staff - Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 14:19)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1988 (Box-folder 14:20)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence and Minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 14:21)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence with Attachments and Minutes, January-April, 1990 (Box-folder 14:22)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence with Attachments and Minutes, May-August, 1990 (Box-folder 14:23)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence with Attachments, September-December, 1990 (Box-folder 14:24)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence with Attachments, January-April, 1991 (Box-folder 14:25)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence with Attachments, May-December, 1991 (Box-folder 14:26)
  - Program Staff - Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 14:27)
  - Staff - Personnel Policies for Professional and Non-Professional Staff, 1971 (Box-folder 14:28)
  - Staff Council - Correspondence and Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 14:29)
  - Staff Council - Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 14:30)
  - Staff Council - Materials, 1986 (Box-folder 14:31)
  - Staff Development Committee - Correspondence, Minutes and Materials, 1991 (Box-folder 14:32)
- Series 9: Other Organizational Records and Materials, 1901-2002
  - 22nd Annual YWCA Outstanding Women Awards - Nomination Form, 2002 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Assorted Notes and Papers, undated (Box-folder 15:2)
  - By-laws, 1966, 1971 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Computer Services, 1984 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Executive Director Job Description, 1969 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Frontlash Voting Rights Mailing, undated (Box-folder 15:6)
  - History - Worldwide YWCA, undated (Box-folder 15:7)
  - History - YWCA Richmond, circa 1970s-1980s, undated (Box-folder 15:8)
  - History - YWCA Richmond - Dillard, Clarissa Kyles, 1988 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - History - YWCA Richmond - Donated Photographs, undated (Box-folder 15:10)
  - History - YWCA Richmond - Leaders and Member Count, 1910, undated (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Letters Received by Mr. John Herrick Moses Regarding YWCA, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - National Girls Work Council Newsletter, 1939 (Box-folder 15:13)
  - Organizational Materials - YWCA mission/history, organizational chart, A1-Board of Directors, Board Policies, Constitution and By-Laws, A2-Board Composition, and Jon Description and Board/Task Force Commitment Form, 1996 (Box-folder 15:14)
  - Organizational Materials - A3-Committees, Assessment Tool Task Force, Public Relations Roster, Communications Plan, Personnel Task Force, Capital/ Building Committee, and Finance Committee Roster, 1996-1999, undated (Box-folder 15:15)
  - Organizational Materials - OWA Committee, Programs Task Force, Action Plan for Child Care Center Evaluation, Development Task Force, Advisory Council, B1-Long Range Planning, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 15:16)
  - Organizational Materials - Strategic Plan, B2-Annual Planning, Annual Plan, DV/Shelter Workplan, SA Workplan, C1-Programs, Operating Budget, C2-Program reviews, and Shelter Evaluation (Consumer), 1995-1999 (Box-folder 15:17)
  - Organizational Materials - Client Goal Sheet, C3-Staff Training, C4-Program Policies, Operational Plicy and Procedures Manual, C5-Accessibility/Consumer Feedback, 1996, 1998, undated (Box-folder 15:18)
  - Organizational Materials - D1-Fiscal Management, D2-Audit, General Environment, Annual Audit, D3-Operational Cash Reserve, D4-Risk Management, and Shelter Client Grievance Procedure, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15:19)
  - Organizational Materials - Confidentiality, Photo Release, D5-Program Cost Reviews, D6- Finance Committee, E1-Fund Development, Receiving/Acknowledging Cash Gifts, Annual Fund Campaign Plan and Receipt of Donations, 1996-1999, undated (Box-folder 15:20)
  - Organizational Materials - E2-Donor Acknowledgement, E3-Fund Development Activities by Board, F1-Marketing/Public Relations Plan, Communications Plan, F2-Client Confidentiality and Privacy in Public Relations, G1-Collaborative Relationships, and Collaborative Agreements, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 15:21)
  - Organizational Materials - H1-Promotion of United Way Partnership, H2-Timely Submission of Required Reports, H3-Support of United Way Fundraising Campaigns, YWCA Lifestories Annual Report, and YWCA Women's Advocacy Program Pamphlets, 1996-1998, undated (Box-folder 15:22)
  - Organizational Materials - I1-Personnel Policies and Procedures, Job Descriptions, I2-Staff Development Supervision/Performance, Personnel Policies and Procedures, I3-Use of Volunteers, J1-Facilities Management, Applicable Permits/Licenses, and Summary Comments/Conclusions Sheet, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 15:23)
  - Report of the Central YWCA Study Committee, Richmond Area Community Council, 1953 (Box-folder 15:24)
  - School Integration Information Sheet, 1970 (Box-folder 15:25)
  - The Searchlight, 1914 (Box-folder 15:26)
  - "Statement and Record of Obligation" in Acceptance of the Constitution of the National Association, 1959 (Box-folder 15:27)
  - This Week in Richmond and Petersburg (Cover Shows YWCA Building on N. Fifth Street and includes YWCA Fall Schedule), 1977 (Box-folder 15:28)
  - YWCA Awareness Survey - Monument Group, 1999 (Box-folder 15:29)
- Series 10: Certificate, Comic, Manuals, Photographs, and Proclamations, 1931-2001
  - Certificate of Recognition, Sexual Assault Awareness Week, 1990 (Box 16:1)
  - Comic: "When a Young Girl Needs a Friend!" by Fred O. Seibel, Richmond-Times Dispatch, January 14, 1931 (Box 16:2)
  - Manual, YWCA Board of Directors, 2001 (Box 16:3)
  - Manual, YWCA Legacy Promise, YWCA 28th National Convention, 1979 (Box 16:4)
  - Photograph, date stone, "YWCA 1887-1913," undated (Box 16:5)
  - Photograph, group of girls lined up in a gymnasium, undated (Box 16:6)
  - Proclamation, City of Richmond, "Domestic Violence Awareness Month," 1995 (Box 16:7)
  - Proclamation, City of Richmond, "YWCA Week," 1992 (Box 16:8)
- Series 11: Architectural Drawings, Floor Plans and Site Plans, 1963-2000
  - Camp Fernlake Architectural and Site Plans including Correspondence, 1963, 1966 (Drawer 74)
  - YWCA Floor Plans including Renovation Plans, Existing and Proposed Plans and Feasibility Study with Floor Plans, 1998, 2000, undated (Drawer 74)